## **BENJAMIN CAURE**

# FREELANCE DEVELOPER & ARCHITECT



Second Second

√ linked.in/in/benjamin-caure

**(3)** +33 7 71 60 66 31

d benjamin.caure@gmail.com

Enthusiastic Fullstack Developer with 10+ years of broad experience in Java and Javascript areas, with willingness to master Node.js, Python, React, React Native and Vue.

## $\textbf{My Projects} \rightarrow \textbf{Check the code!}$

Tech Blog Author at Baeldung baeldung.com/author/benjamincaure

Coding game:gitlab.com/pjben/tp-binome-1

## **My Work Experience**

#### **BECOMS**

### March 2022 to present Architect - Full-stack Developer

Application Development for Small/Medium Business



- Requirements analysis and development of the solution: API, Web Apps, Mobile Apps (PWA)
- Develop with React, Typescript, Tailwind, React-Query, NodeJS, Express, Mongoose, Mongodb
- Build solutions based on open-source software integration (API / Webhook)
- Integration of Cloud services (Auth0, AWS S3, Azure)

Stack: React, Node.js, Express, Mongo DB, Typescript, Tailwind, React Query

Softwares: Dolibarr, CEGID, Sage, AWS, Azure, Auth0

#### **BACARDI**

#### Jan 2021 to Feb 2022 **Developer / Software Architect**



MixlabCocktails.com - Mobile App + Website for **Bacardi Consumers** 

- · Design the software architecture
- Develop with React, React-Native and Node.js
- Cloud services integration: Headless CMS, IAM, search engine
- English-speaking environment

React Native, React, Node.js, Azure Functions, Gigya, Algolia, Contentful, Firebase, Google Cloud Platform

#### **OTHER EXPERIENCES**

More details on bcaure.github.io

2018-2020	Full-stack developer - Minister of Research
2016-2017	Mobile developer - Software Architect - Michelin
2013-2015	Java Developer - Software Architect - Michelin
2010-2013	Java Lead Developer - Minister of Agriculture
2009-2010	Functional Analyst - Michelin
2008-2009	Devops Jenkins - Michelin
2006-2008	Java Developer - Crédit Agricole (bank)
2005-2006	.Net Developer - Nestlé, Les Mousquetaires (Mass Retail)

## **Education & Skills**

#### ISIMA -Master School of IT

Frontend: Javascript/Typescript, React, Angular, RxJs, Redux, React-Native, Ionic Backend: Node.js, Express, Java, Spring, Gitlab CI, Docker, Google Cloud, MS Azure

Management: Architecture (integration, security, Fluent in english, thanks to several years of data, infra), Agile, Team Leader

work with remote coworkers